Emma: Hello, stranger!
Ben: Emma!
Emma: Sorry I’m late.
Ben: Don’t worry, it’s fine.
How are you?
Emma: Great! It’s so nice to see you…
You look a bit thin.
Are you eating enough?
Ben: Yes, I am.
You sound like Mom.
Anyway, this is Carla.
Carla: Hi. It’s nice to meet you.
Emma: It’s nice to meet you, too.
Emma: How’s the photography course going?
Ben: It’s great.
Right now, I’m working on a really big project.
It’s going well, but it’s hard work.
Ben: Hi, Izzy.
This is Emma. Emma, Izzy.
Izzy: Hi, Emma. It’s really nice to meet you.
Emma: It’s so good to meet you, too.
Izzy: I’ve heard a lot about you.
Emma: Me too.
Wow, that’s a really cool jacket!
Izzy: Oh, thanks.
Ben: Coffee?
Izzy: Yeah. A flat white, please.
Izzy: So, have you seen much of London yet?
Emma: Just the hotel room.
I only arrived last night.
But we’re going to go out for dinner later.
Are you going to come with us?
Izzy: Um… no, sorry, I can’t.
I’m going out for drinks with the people from my office…
Um, team building…
Emma: Oh… team building…
Izzy: … So yeah, I work long hours, but I love it.
Emma: That’s great. Ben, Izzy can’t come with us.
She needs to meet some people from work, or something?
Ben: Really, Izzy?
Emma just got here.
I booked a table for three.
We could see some sights on the way.
Izzy: I’d love to…
I’d really love to.
But it’s a work thing.
Everyone is going.
It’s really important that I’m there.
Ben: Well… if it’s important.
Emma: It’s fine, Ben.
You can’t expect Izzy to change her plans just because I’m here.
It’s just you and me, then.
Ben: Do you really need to go to this work thing?
Izzy: Yes.
I’m sorry…
Actually, I need to go now.
Ben: But you just got here.
Izzy: I know… I just… I’m sorry.
Nice to meet you, Emma.
Let’s do something really soon – maybe tomorrow – the three of us?
Emma: Sure.